

## **OLEKSANDR UNTERVALD**

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

## CONTACT

- +38093 060 22 46
- untervaldthebest@gmail.co
- Ukraine, Kiyv
- in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/oleks-andr-untervald">www.linkedin.com/in/oleks</a> andr-untervald
- @hunter999999
- f <a href="https://www.facebook.com/oleksandr.untervald">https://www.facebook.com/oleksandr.untervald</a>
- https://github.com/Oleksan drUntervald
- https://untervald-frontend-cv.vercel.app/

## **SKILLS**

- HTML5
- CSS / SASS / TAILWINDCSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT / REDUX
- NEXT.JS
- VITE / GULP / WEBPUCK
- GIT / GITHUB
- FIGMA

#### LANGUAGES

- English (B1)
- Uktaine (native)

# EDUCATION

**GENERAL EDUCATION** 

2016 Kyiv "University of Modern Knowledge" DEP-LOW

**IT EDUCATION** 

Esfirum IT School Frontend 2021 - 2022

Okten SCHOOL FULL STACK 2024 - in the process

8

## **PROFILE**

I am a passionate front-end developer with experience in building responsive and interactive websites. I am proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and modern frameworks like React and Next.js. I focus on creating user-friendly interfaces and enhancing web performance. Currently, I am working on personal projects to further develop my skills and stay up-to-date with the latest web technologies.



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **PET PROJECTS**

FRONT-END FIELD

 I am currently focusing on developing my skills through the creation of personal pet projects. These projects allow me to explore and implement various web technologies while enhancing my understanding of front-end development. You can check my pet projects here: <u>UnterCV</u> or on my <u>GITHUB</u>!

#### **PET PROJECTS LIST:**

name / technologies: JSHUB / JS,CSS,HTML

description: Eplore Interactive Challenges or Mini Games with JavaScript.

Link: <a href="https://js-unter-hub.vercel.app/">https://js-unter-hub.vercel.app/</a>

GitHub: https://github.com/OleksandrUntervald/JSUnterHub

**name / technologies**: my CV / JS,CSS,HTML **description**: My current and relevant portfolio site.

Link: https://js-unter-hub.vercel.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/OleksandrUntervald/JSUnterHub

NAME / TECHNOLOGIES: PROFESSIONAL CV / NEXT. JS, TAILWINDCSS, VITE

description: An example of creating a portfolio site

Link: <a href="https://js-unter-hub.vercel.app/">https://js-unter-hub.vercel.app/</a>

#### Frontend-developer & Media Buyer

2021/10 - 2022/09

2024 - PRESENT

company: Imonetizet

- Creation, deploy and service of landing pages using: HTML, CSS, JS.
- Setting up a redirect, working with servers and domains.
- Setting up the cloaca robot with Keitaro: creating streams, loading Black/White pages, PostBack. Was responsible for proxy procurement.